marketingcheckpoint.com 2009-05-30

# Privacy Policy | Marketing Checkpoint

**Please carefully read this _privacy policy_ document. It contains important information regarding user information privacy.**

 **Your account**

As a MarketingCheckpoint.com user, the information we collect, such as first name, last name, location, and e-mail address, is collected as you knowingly choose to disclose to us. Such information may be kept private depending on settings but there is no guarantee that the information you disclose is out of the reach of unwanted harvestors. If you are not interested in provided required information, we ask you to not register an account, nor do so with false information as prohibited and in violation of the Terms of Use.

MarketingCheckpoint.com will never sell or otherwise redistribute your personal information for any reason except in connection with a law enforcement investigation or government agency, or with a necessary part of the website.

**Collected information**

At MarketingCheckpoint.com, we collect two primary sources of information - that in which you manually input to your account and website information such as your browser type and IP address while you interact on our website.

As a registered user, you are asked and required to provide certain indentifiable information for legal and communicative purposes. Such information includes and is not limited to first name, last name, e-mail address, town/city, state, and birthdate.

When using MarketingCheckpoint.com, you can edit your profile, add content, create groups, write reviews, send private messages, and so on. This content and information is collected in order to provide a growing and continuous experience for users. It allows users to return to MarketingCheckpoint.com to view past messages and previously posted content. There is no guarantee that such information is saved or backed up, however we do try to maintain a backup of information each night.

**Posted content**

As a user, you have the privilege to share content. This may be blogs, messages, comments, data, and even directory listings. We offer no guarantee to the security of user posted content in any means, nor do we guarantee that user posted content is safe from unauthorized users. Please be advised that user posted content is shared at your own risk.

You understand that user content that you may edit or remove is not guaranteed to be permanently edited or removed entirely. We reserve the right to save any and all content along with any and all versions.

**Age requirement**

Children (15) years old and younger are prohibited from joining and registering at MarketingCheckpoint.com. We do not collect, redistribute, or sell information from children (15) years old and younger. Attempting to register for an account at MarketingCheckpoint.com at an age of (15) or younger is strictly prohibited. If a user is found to have registered and is (15) years old or younger, their account will be terminated immediately, unless direct parent consent is provided. Please use our contact form if you believe we have information for or a user who is under (15) years old or younger.

Users who are between 16 and 18 years old are highly recommended to get parental consent prior to sending information about themselves to us, such as registering an account at MarketingCheckpoint.com.

**Third parties**

MarketingCheckpoint.com is a community that is strongly built on user posted content. Such content is sometimes accessible by outside sources who have no direct relationship to MarketingCheckpoint.com. As well, a third party such as a friend or other user may access user posted content at any time. We cannot control or guarantee how a third party uses such content.

Third party sources may request personal information but we will only share such information when it is safely needed to offer a certain service, or legally necessary such as with a government agency, or with your direct consent.

**Advertisements**

Unless otherwise stated, MarketingCheckpoint.com does not endorse advertisements, but they are provided as a way to offer targeted advertising to the community. Third party advertisements and parties may record tracking information about you such as an IP address when visiting their website or ad. We do not control where the ads go nor do we monitor or guarantee the safety of visiting such advertisements. 

**Website use**

As a GOGGLES ON user, you understand the privacy policy and agree to the above. At any time there may be revisions to this policy without notice. It is the responsibility of the user to check this policy page frequently for changes.
